<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome on Dive Rinse Repeat Scuba, LLC</title>
    <link>https://drrscuba.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome on Dive Rinse Repeat Scuba, LLC</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://drrscuba.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://drrscuba.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 16:20:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drrscuba.com/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Open Water Diver</title>
      <link>https://drrscuba.com/classes/aow/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drrscuba.com/classes/aow/</guid>
      <description>The PADI Advanced Open Water Diver course improves your underwater knowledge and skills. Any Open Water Diver can enroll regardless of your skill level. The course helps you build confidence in navigation and deep water dives and introduces you to different diving activities such as wreck diving, night diving or underwater photography. After completing your eLearning, you’ll make five Adventure Dives: a deep dive (beyond 60 feet), a navigation dive, and three additional Adventure Dives of your choice to earn your certification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discover Scuba Diving</title>
      <link>https://drrscuba.com/classes/discover/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drrscuba.com/classes/discover/</guid>
      <description>Find out what scuba is all about with a PADI Discover Scuba Diving course.
You&amp;rsquo;ll experience an instructor led introduction to the underwater world. While not a scuba certification course, you&amp;rsquo;ll learn what it is like to breathe underwater and what is involved in becoming a full fledge scuba diver.
To sign up for a PADI Discover Scuba Diving experience, you must be at least 10 years old. No prior experience with scuba diving is necessary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dive Travel</title>
      <link>https://drrscuba.com/services/travel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drrscuba.com/services/travel/</guid>
      <description>Content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Divemaster</title>
      <link>https://drrscuba.com/classes/divemaster/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drrscuba.com/classes/divemaster/</guid>
      <description>Share your passion for scuba diving by becoming a PADI Divemaster. As a divemaster you’ll supervise scuba diving activities and assist with scuba classes. PADI Divemaster is the first step in your diving career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Duane Newman</title>
      <link>https://drrscuba.com/team/duane/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drrscuba.com/team/duane/</guid>
      <description>Duane is a PADI Master Scuba Diver Trainer and when he isn’t teaching can usually be found diving with his camera in hand. After experiencing his own challenges becoming certified, and then falling in love with scuba, he pressed on to become an instructor so he could help others overcome their fears and discover the amazing underwater world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gear Purchases</title>
      <link>https://drrscuba.com/services/gear/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drrscuba.com/services/gear/</guid>
      <description>Content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Krista Block</title>
      <link>https://drrscuba.com/team/krista/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drrscuba.com/team/krista/</guid>
      <description>Krista is a PADI Master Scuba Diver Trainer and when she isn’t teaching you can find her underwater, spinning around, playing with nearby aquatic life. Krista enjoys all types of diving, but especially loves shark, wreck, and macro dives. One of her biggest accomplishments in Scuba, besides earning her MSDT, is obtaining a Tech 50 Certification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lisa Newman</title>
      <link>https://drrscuba.com/team/lisa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drrscuba.com/team/lisa/</guid>
      <description>Lisa is a Master Scuba Diver and loves being in the water, whether at the lake or ocean. One of her passions is knowing all the fish and aquatic life she comes across, she always has her fish ID book close by.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maintenance</title>
      <link>https://drrscuba.com/services/maintenance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drrscuba.com/services/maintenance/</guid>
      <description>Content</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master Scuba Diver</title>
      <link>https://drrscuba.com/classes/master/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drrscuba.com/classes/master/</guid>
      <description>Join the best of the best in recreational scuba diving and live the dive life as a PADI Master Scuba Diver. The Master Scuba Diver rating places you in an elite group of respected divers who have earned this rating through both significant experience and scuba training. Fewer than two percent of divers ever achieve this rating. When you flash your Master Scuba Diver card, people know that you’ve spent time underwater in a variety of environments and had your share of dive adventures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Water Diver</title>
      <link>https://drrscuba.com/classes/owsd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drrscuba.com/classes/owsd/</guid>
      <description>During the PADI Open Water Diver course, you’ll learn what you need to know to explore the underwater world using scuba. The PADI Open Water Diver course includes three parts: Knowledge Development, Confined Water Dives, and Open Water Dives.
Knowledge Development covers the principles, concepts and terms you need to know for dive safety and enjoyment.
During the Confined Water Dives, you learn and practice scuba skills in a pool or water with pool-like conditions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rescue Diver</title>
      <link>https://drrscuba.com/classes/rescue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drrscuba.com/classes/rescue/</guid>
      <description>The PADI Rescue Diver course teaches you techniques to avoid and manage problems and improve your confidence as a diver. During the course you’ll become a better buddy by enhancing your ability to identify potential problems and by practicing dive emergency protocol. The subject is serious but the training is fun – many divers tell us the PADI Rescue Diver course was their favorite</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>