<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Meet Our Team on Dive Rinse Repeat Scuba, LLC</title>
    <link>https://drrscuba.com/team/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Meet Our Team on Dive Rinse Repeat Scuba, LLC</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://drrscuba.com/team/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Billy Wilson</title>
      <link>https://drrscuba.com/team/billy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drrscuba.com/team/billy/</guid>
      <description>Billy is a Rescue Diver working on his PADI Divemaster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Duane Newman</title>
      <link>https://drrscuba.com/team/duane/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drrscuba.com/team/duane/</guid>
      <description>Duane is a PADI Master Scuba Diver Trainer and when he isn’t teaching can usually be found diving with his camera in hand. After experiencing his own challenges becoming certified, and then falling in love with scuba, he pressed on to become an instructor so he could help others overcome their fears and discover the amazing underwater world. He is a Public Safety Diver with the all volunteer Lee&amp;rsquo;s Summit Underwater Rescue dive team, where he also serves as the current Training Officer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Krista Block</title>
      <link>https://drrscuba.com/team/krista/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drrscuba.com/team/krista/</guid>
      <description>Krista became Open Water Certified in 2014 and was instantly hooked on Scuba! She is a PADI Master Scuba Diver Trainer and has been an instructor since 2018. As a Disabled Divers International Assistant Diver (she is working her way towards instructor) she is able to teach divers at any physical level. When she isn’t teaching you can find her underwater, spinning around, playing with nearby aquatic life. Krista enjoys all types of diving, but especially loves shark, wreck, and macro dives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lisa Newman</title>
      <link>https://drrscuba.com/team/lisa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://drrscuba.com/team/lisa/</guid>
      <description>Lisa is a Master Scuba Diver and loves being in the water, whether at the lake or ocean. One of her passions is knowing all the fish and aquatic life she comes across, she always has her fish ID book close by.
Lisa also works as a child care provider for 3 active daughters of school teachers. Growing up in an educator&amp;rsquo;s household she knows how crazy it can be and loves being &amp;ldquo;Aunt Lisa&amp;rdquo; to these girls.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
